I thought you weren't coming.
Why did you have Andrew
beaten up?
So, what's next?
Are you going to take down
me and Peter
because we already know
the truth?
That you're part
of the syndicate?
I came here
because I was worried
about Andrew.
But you're accusing me
of so many things.
We placed a tracker
on Jin Ho's car.
The last movement recorded
was at Bolivar Mushroom Chips
Manufacturing.
We'll expedite a search warrant.
And good thing,
I already spoke with the DDE.
Peter, why are you
calling Jin Ho?
I just want Jin Ho
to save himself.
This is our chance to bring down
the syndicate.
Can you promise
that when you arrest Jin Ho,
- you won't hurt him?
- I'll try.
[OBB]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE RINGS]
[OPERATOR SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY
ON PHONE]
Check the number
and dial again.
[PHONE CHIMES]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[GATE CREAKS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, Mom...
Yes?
- Joey?
- Did you see Peter?
No, I didn't notice him.
He could be outside.
He's not there either,
and his cell phone is gone.
Did he go home?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Stay here, okay?
I'll just go upstairs.
Okay, Mom.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Why is no one here?
Could Jin Ho be here?
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello, Joey?
Peter, why did you
suddenly disappear?
Did you go home?
Joey, don't be mad, okay?
But I'm at the warehouse
to warn Jin Ho.
What?
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
Peter?
What are you doing here?
[BRAZEN MUSIC PLAYING]
[OPERATOR SPEAKING ON PHONE]
Please try again later.
Peter, come on!
Mom, I'm going out
to meet Peter.
It's important.
Joey...
I know I hurt you.
I'm sorry.
[BRAZEN MUSIC PLAYING]
No, that's wrong.
Joey...
I know you're angry with me.
I'm sorry.
Joey...
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Where is she going?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Answer me.
Why did you come here?
To warn you.
You need to leave.
- Why?
- What do you mean why?
The DDE and the police
are coming here.
They're going to raid
this place.
They're going to come after you.
What?
How did they know this place?
They put a tracker on your car
when we met.
We need to leave
before they catch us, come on!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[KNOCKING]
Who's there?
We have a search warrant!
Where's your boss?
Who's inside?
Ma'am, Sir, the two of us
are just guards here.
No one's inside.
What do you mean no one?
You can search the place.
That's exactly what we'll do!
Secure this!
- Come with us!
- Yes, Sir.
Come with us!
- You need to go.
- What?
No time to explain,
just leave now.
No, we're leaving together,
us both.
Listen, Peter!
I need you to get out of here.
Stop those cops and tell them
not to go inside.
No, you're coming with me.
Just do what you're told!
Go!
[GATE CREAKS]
Move!
[BRAZEN MUSIC CONTINUES]
Joey.
Andrew...
what are you doing here?
I followed you.
And you, what are you doing
here?
This looks like an official
operation, Joey.
You're not allowed here.
Peter followed Jin Ho
to warn him.
He might get trapped inside.
I couldn't just leave him.
There you go again.
You're being reckless again.
Joey, you're rushing
into decisions again.
So what?
I'm not letting you go there.
Andrew, you're not my parent
nor my boyfriend to stop me.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Get inside!
[GUN COCKS]
Men, move!
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[GUN COCKS]
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
Why is no one here?
Where are they?
Even the evidence is gone.
[RATTLES]
Ambush! Cover!
[EXPLOSIONS]
[GUN FIRING]
Joey!
This way, come!
This way! This way!
[GUN FIRING IN DISTANCE]
Joey, I told you,
you're not ready
for situations like this.
Fine, you're right!
Let's go home then.
But what about Peter?
He's still inside!
You have to leave now!
What about you?
If you don't leave,
I'll stay too.
So when they arrive,
I'll tell them
you didn't fight back.
None of them will survive here.
This is an ambush!
What?
[GUN FIRING]
There's nowhere to run!
You can't beat me
at my own game.
What about you?
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Don't you want to go there?
I'll give a big prize
to whoever kills the most.
Go on, finish them all!
Take this phone and just go!
Now! Leave now!
Go! Go!
[GUN FIRING IN DISTANCE]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- Peter!
- Joey, come on!
Peter...
Thank goodness you're okay.
Jin Ho saved me.
But why isn't he with you?
He said those who went inside
won't survive.
He said this is an ambush.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
The plan worked.
Miguel and the stupid DDE agents
all took the bait.
Tell me everything.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm watching them fall
one by one.
I'm sure they regret storming
this warehouse.
Don't let that "ghost" cop
get out alive.
He made a fool of me.
Now, I want him riddled
with bullets
so his real burial could happen.
That's exactly why I wanted
to do this.
Good thing you agreed.
I must admit,
I had apprehensions
about your plan.
We expect to lose a lot.
But I realized...
we also gain much
once the enemies are eliminated.
We need to move
to a bigger location
for our operations.
Anyway, congratulations to you
and your people.
Don't delay it anymore.
Yes, Berdugo.
See you at the new place.
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
You look happy.
What's that call about?
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
I just had a big win today
because a huge hindrance
will be gone.
What hindrance?
A business rival?
A huge enemy.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
We need to go to dad!
What? You'll rush into
the middle of a gunfight?
Joey, you can't help them
inside.
Your father might get distracted
and you could put him
in more danger.
So, what do we do?
I'll call Chief.
I'll ask for back up.
Joey, calm down.
Jin Ho is inside.
He'll find a way
to save your father.
Really? Will he do that?
You're not even sure
if he's still on our side.
He will.
He already let me escape
so nothing would happen to me.
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
I didn't want it to go to waste.
You knew they were coming?
Yes, because you led them here.
I didn't do anything.
You don't realize it,
but you're the one
who led them here.
Ma'am, someone's here.
Delgado?
He's back from the dead.
We'll follow him.
No.
I have a better idea.
So, Joey's father is alive?
All flesh and bones.
That means you followed me.
You don't trust me?
It hurts to be betrayed,
doesn't it?
That's exactly how I felt
when I realized
your friend exposed me.
- What are you talking about?
- Oh, come on, Jin Ho!
You know it was the girl
in the hoodie.
And you know I've been
looking for her
so I can get back at her
for all the problems
she caused me.
But you kept her away from me!
Because when I was with her,
and other friends,
they showed me kindness.
Kindness, yes.
Kindness...
you're a fool, Jin Ho.
She is just using you.
She met with you to plant
a tracker
and that lead them here.
Do you think they care
if you die?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I don't think so.
So why would you care
about them?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
That's done.
Prove your loyalty!
- [GUN FIRING]
- [INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[GUN FIRING]
[INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[INTENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GUN FIRING]
[GUN COCKS]
[BULLETS PLINKING]
[GUN FIRING]
Are you okay?
I'm fine, Sir!
Let's finish this!
[GUN FIRING IN DISTANCE]
[GUN FIRING]
[INTENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Stop!
Hands up!
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
Liza De Leon!
Jin Ho!
You're under arrest!
Put your guns down!
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Did you talk to them?
The police are on their way,
and the DDE agents have backup.
Good thing there's
reinforcement.
Joey, we need to leave.
That's Chief Lansang's order.
Andrew, I don't want to!
I won't leave while my father
is inside,
fighting for his life!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Do you really think
you can defeat us that easily?
Nothing here is easy!
I was imprisoned,
I almost got killed,
and torn away from my family!
Poor Miguel Delgado.
What do you want me to do?
Cry over your tragic life?
You're coming with us...
and you'll reveal
the syndicate's secret,
and who Berdugo really is!
So, what now,
are we just going to sit here?
Wait, let me check if it's safe.
Stay here.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Come on, let's go!
Hey!
Put your guns down!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I said put them down!
Put them down!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hey, let go of that!
- [THUDDING]
- [BRAZEN MUSIC PLAYING]
Andrew, Peter!
[GRUNTING]
[THUDS]
- [THUDDING]
- [GRUNTING]
[THUDS]
- [CLANKS]
- [THUDS]
- [THUDDING]
- [GRUNTING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [THUDDING]
- [GRUNTING]
[THUDS]
[WHACKS]
- [THUDDING]
- [GRUNTING]
[GROANS]
[THUDDING]
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Dad, where are you?
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
You can't make me confess!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
You'll get nothing from me!
And besides...
none of you
will leave here alive!
Zoey!
- [GUN FIRING]
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[ZOEY GROANS]
[GUN FIRING]
Madam, let's go!
Go ahead, I will cover you.
[GUN FIRING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ZOEY GROANS]
Zoey!
[GUN FIRING]
Go after Liza!
There! I'll cover for you!
[GUN FIRING]
[ZOEY PANTING]
Zoey...
Sir, it hurts,
I don't want to die yet.
That won't happen.
We still need you.
[ZOEY GRUNTS]
Apply pressure on your wound.
[ZOEY GROANING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
- Joey!
Come on, Peter!
[GUN FIRING]
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
Call Joey, quick!
[PHONE RINGING]
Sorry, Peter,
I'll talk to you later.
I still need to see dad.
[RINGING CONTIUES]
Joey isn't answering.
I hope she's okay.
Let's go!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[ZOEY WHIMPERING]
Where's the back up?
We need the back up now!
[ZOEY GROANING]
[GUN FIRING]
Zoey, you might bleed out here.
We're leaving.
Let's go.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[ZOEY GROANING]
[INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
They waited until
we were all inside
before they opened fire.
They prepared for this.
Clean this mess up.
We'll still bring down
the syndicate.
But you know, I realized...
I'm here to kill you.
Do it, Jin Ho!
Didn't she betray you?
Jin Ho, don't, please.
You used me to get Liza.
Have a safe trip to hell, Joey.
Andrew, I'm begging you.
Don't report this to Tirada yet.
Major, I'm not here to cover.
I came for Joey.
Joey?
Jin Ho took her, Major.
What?